<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Refat</string>
    <string name="conttent">
        I am Refat Akbar.I have completed my graduation in Computer Science and Engineering
        from United International University(UIU)on October, 2015 bearing CGPA
        3.59 on a scale of 4.I passed SSC 2010 from Mohammadpur girls High School
        and HSC from Mohammadpur Preparatory Girls College with GPA 5.I like to reading book,writing,
        Singing and painting.I have been a competent student with having programming language skill
        like JAVA,  HTML5, CSS3, JAVASCRIPT, ANDROID,C etc. I have also done a course on android and graphics
        design. I have experience to go thorough Database like MySQL  as
        well as technical tools like Eclips,Android Studio,Netbeans,Visual Studio etc. during my academic
        curriculum.I have attached my work experience in my portfolio.




    </string>
    <string name="bengali">
        The objective of my project was translate signs to letter.So that deaf people
        language to be understood by the people out of deaf community.I work on this project
        only translate Bengali langauge.I build a tool for the people who is unable to hear and speak.
        My system is one kind of bridge between deaf,dumb and normal people.My system is cost effective.
        So that the poor background people may also use my system.I applied technical tools Matlab and Visual  Studio for
        build my project.The whole project was divided into 8 step which was Feature Extraction,Image Processing,
        Segmentation,Database,Recognition,Experimental Results and Analysis,Classification and the last one was Conclusion.
        I have used K-nearest neighbor algorithm in classification step which give the output which dataset is nearest.
        After all of these process completing I was calculated the accuracy of matching image.And I got 75 percent matching
        image accuracy.
    </string>
    <string name="online">
          My website was about online shopping which name was Collection.Nowadays online shopping
        is so popular.It is too much tough for busy people to get enough time for shopping.So for
        this purpose I have decided to make a project about online shopping so people can easily buy
        their necessary products.To build my online project I applied technical tools Netbeans  with database
        MySql.I used the code HTML5,CSS3,PHP,JAVASCRIPT and Bootstrap to develop my website.I used javascript
        to made image slideshow.I also applied javascript in order page.It is my first website with database,
        mysql,php,javascript.I hope I will build a better website than this in future.

        </string>
    <string name="coffee">
        This is my website which was about Online Coffee Shop.It was just like cafeteria website.
        In this website I keep a menu option where different type of flavoured coffees existed.
        People can be register and they can also login in my website.And they can order any kind of
        flavoured coffee whatever they want.I used Netbeans as a technical tools.I applied HTML5,
        CSS3 and JAVASCRIPT.
    </string>
    <string name="temparature">
        This is my first android app which is convert any  number Celsius to Farenheight
        or Farenheight to Celsius.This is my first android app.My app is only convert integer
        number.In my app user can take input by help of some button.And there are 2 button.
        One is for convert input number Celsius to Farenheight and another is for convert the number
        Farenheight to Celsius.

</string>
</resources>
